export default {
  name: "Spanish Words: Body Parts",
  cards: [
    { front: "vertebra", back: "(la) vértebra" },
    { front: "testicle", back: "(el) testículo" },
    { front: "neck", back: "(el) cuello" },
    { front: "bladder", back: "(la) vejiga" },
    { front: "vagina", back: "(la) vagina" },
    { front: "liver", back: "(el) hígado" },
    { front: "lung", back: "(el) pulmón" },
    { front: "kidney", back: "(el) riñón" },
    { front: "rib", back: "(la) costilla" },
    { front: "eye", back: "(el) ojo" },
    { front: "leg", back: "(la) pierna" },
    { front: "tongue", back: "(la) lengua" },
    { front: "nerve", back: "(el) nervio" },
    { front: "cheek", back: "(la) mejilla" },
    { front: "finger", back: "(el) dedo" },
    { front: "mouth", back: "(la) boca" },
    { front: "intestine", back: "(el) intestino" },
    { front: "shoulder", back: "(el) hombro" },
    { front: "heart", back: "(el) corazón" },
    { front: "back (part of body)", back: "(la) espalda" },
    { front: "index finger", back: "(el) dedo índice" },
    { front: "bosom", back: "(la) mama" },
    { front: "fingernail", back: "(la) uña" },
    { front: "beard", back: "(la) barba" },
    { front: "head", back: "(la) cabeza" },
    { front: "hand", back: "(la) mano" },
    { front: "nose", back: "(la) nariz" },
    { front: "arm", back: "(el) brazo" },
    { front: "hair", back: "(el) cabello" },
    { front: "forehead", back: "(la) frente" },
    { front: "vein", back: "(la) vena" },
    { front: "little finger", back: "(el) dedo meñique" },
    { front: "chin", back: "(la) barbilla" },
    { front: "lip", back: "(el) labio" },
    { front: "thumb", back: "(el) pulgar" },
    { front: "stomach", back: "(el) estómago" },
    { front: "belly", back: "(el) vientre" },
    { front: "tooth", back: "(el) diente" },
    { front: "skeleton", back: "(el) esqueleto" },
    { front: "penis", back: "(el) pene" },
    { front: "ring finger", back: "(el) dedo anular" },
    { front: "brain", back: "(el) cerebro" },
    { front: "bottom", back: "(el) trasero" },
    { front: "sperm", back: "(el) esperma" },
    { front: "middle finger", back: "(el) dedo del medio" },
    { front: "ear", back: "(la) oreja" },
    { front: "knee", back: "(la) rodilla" },
    { front: "artery", back: "(la) arteria" },
    { front: "bone (part of body)", back: "(el) hueso" },
    { front: "spine", back: "(la) espina dorsal" },
    { front: "heel", back: "(el) talón" },
    { front: "foot", back: "(el) pie" },
    { front: "muscle", back: "(el) músculo" },
    { front: "toe", back: "(el) dedo del pie" },
  ],
};